[funky hip-hop beat layers in]
[older Kanan]
Previously on Raising Kanan...
It's my understanding
that Lump Maxwell
has been backing
your current operation.
Been with Lumps
since he was runnin' numbers
in Saint Albany's.
[grunting]
[gunshots]
-What's all of this?
-That shit ain't ours.
'Cause them white boys.
they dimed you to fuck out.
Your services are
no longer required.
I ain't the kind of nigga
you could just replace.
This whole thing with you.
has fucked with my head.
I ain't got time to listen
to all this noise right now.
Fuck you Kanan.
Fuck you too. bitch.
Your best and only chance
at winning this thing.
is your daughter.
Bet the fucking house on her.
-You killed famous.
-[gunshots]
Without you and the Columbian.
Raq's business is done.
And if her business is dead.
she's of no use
to Pino Bernardi.
There's nothin' left to say.
She's leavin'.
We have surveillance
of you meeting with both
Stefano Marchetti and Pino
Bernardi on multiple occasions.
We're in a bad place here.
[gun cocks]
[Flossie] So your son broke into
my apartment last night.
He told me he swapped out those
drugs that killed the judge.
And he also told me
that you knew.
We're done.
Your brother is the only reason
you're not dead already.
[Marvin]
If somethin' happens to me.
just make sure that case
get to my daughter.
[gunshots]
[Marvin] This gon' stay with you
for a while. boy.
You gon' see me
in your nightmares.
♪
♪ I'm a hustla. baby ♪
-♪ I'm a hustla. baby ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I know heartbreaks
Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through
The ups and downs ♪
♪ You know I get around ♪
♪ So to me. it's all a part
Of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke man
Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure. man
I gotta take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turn homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Make money
Make-make-make money ♪
♪ When shit hit the fan
We'll take money. Southside ♪
♪ Beef with the best of 'em
Done shot at the rest of 'em ♪
♪ Checks. I'm collectin' 'em
Check. boy. I'm finessin' 'em ♪
♪ Big bags of bread ♪
♪ Boy. you fuck around
Put a big bag on your head ♪
♪ 'Fore the weather break
You're dead ♪
♪ Let's get to it ♪
♪ They don't do it
Like we do it ♪
♪ Cop it. whip it
Bag it. flip it ♪
♪ Re-up. we up
G'd up. what up? ♪
♪ Runnin' 'round this bitch
Still not givin' a fuck ♪
♪ When it come to that paper
There'll be no complications ♪
♪ Ha-ha. that's right ♪
♪ Put a hole in a nigga
Right in front of you ♪
♪ Your heartbeat pacin' ♪
♪ And it's alright ♪
♪ That's how we do it
On this side ♪
♪ Niggas get to it
♪ I know heartbreaks
Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through
The ups and downs ♪
♪ You know I get around ♪
♪ So to me. it's all a part
Of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke man
Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure. man
I gotta take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turn homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Ayy. ayy ♪
[Rileyy vocalization]
[solemn music playing]
[older Kanan] Even when you
ain't got shit left.
tell yourself it ain't over.
That you can take what got took.
That you can get back
what got lost.
You might even be able
to grab some corner or block.
maybe even pullin' some soldiers
to fuck with you for a minute.
But the shit that matters most.
your heart.
your soul.
they gone nigga.
And they gone for good.
♪
[sniffling]
I'm not asking you for anything.
'cause I don't need
anything from you.
I just wanted you to know.
And I want you to know
that I'm keeping it.
How you know it's mine?
-This boy.
-I'm just sayin'.
The shit's not crazy to ask.
Meanwhile. you' been makin'
your money.
I know for sure I ain't the
only nigga you been with.
I use protection with
all my dates. Kanan.
It's not like
I'm trying to get you back
to some pathetic shit like that.
And I don't even know
if this means anything to you.
but you're gonna be a father.
And I thought you should know.
that's all.
It means something to me.
Jarita.
If you want to be involved. cool.
If not. that's cool too.
♪
I gotta go.
I guess I'll either hear
from you or I won't.
Whatever.
[door closes]
♪
You think that shit's true
about Richard Gere?
Who the fuck is Richard Gere?
He was in that
Pretty Woman bullshit.
Don't you remember
how everybody was saying
he had to go to the hospital.
'cause he had a gerbil
up his ass?
Right. right. That guy.
Yeah.
That shit's true. no doubt.
Gotta be I mean.
everyone's heard about it.
[coughing]
It's my favorite white boys.
Breeze.
What the fuck?
Man. I thought you people
live better than this.
Y'all living like
niggas out here.
How'd you even find our address?
Police you talkin' to. told me.
Yo. we wasn't talkin'
to the police.
[gunshots]
[menacing music playing]
[dogs barking in background]
Appreciate you
agreeing to sit with me.
Well.
I heard about your brother.
Least I can do.
My. uh. condolences. by the way.
Thank you.
Look. I know you think
I'm out of business.
but I've been in worse spots
than this Mr. Bernardi.
and I always found my way back.
You been in worse spots.
than your son
killing your brother?
I'd hate to be at your house
for Thanksgiving.
Don't tell me.
You didn't know?
Where you hear
that about my son?
It's current scuttlebutt.
I assumed you knew.
I'm not here to talk to
you about all that.
Well. if I were you. that's
all I'd be talking about.
I need you to look out
for me. Mr. Bernardi.
Get my back with Stefano
for a little bit
until I'm back up and running.
that's all.
He wants you dead.
Don't know what
the hell it is with him.
Maybe it's cause he
wanted to mess with me.
and I didn't want to mess
with him in the same way.
Stefano wanted to fuck you.
and you didn't want to fuck him.
Without you.
I'm vulnerable out here.
You know.
Stefano and I grew up together.
Yeah. right off fourth Avenue.
I was 187. He was 188.
He was an athlete.
Baseball. football. basketball-
anything with a fuckin' ball.
One of those guys looked like
he always had a fuckin' tan.
Cocksucker...
Got all the girls.
Me?
I was a fucking asthmatic.
Couldn't even leave the house
till I was seventeen.
And even then.
I was so fuckin' pale.
My skin was translucent.
I- I-you could see right
through the fuckin' veins.
Girls wouldn't even
spit in my direction.
And then-
Lo and behold.
along comes Doris DeFazio.
She lived next door.
I don't know
if she was taking pity on me
or she was just lonely.
like I was.
We started going matinees
together every Saturday.
It was Captains Courageous
at the Savoy.
We were sitting up in the
balcony and out of nowhere.
Doris leans over and kisses me.
Greatest moment
of my fuckin' life.
I been married twice.
I had three kids.
But that day with Doris.
I had a-what do you call it?
An-an out-of-body experience.
First and best kiss I ever got.
Been chasing it ever since.
One week later.
Doris was goin' steady
with Stefano Marchetti.
He had to have all the girls.
I always wanted to do to
him what he did to me.
Don't know what this got to do
with our business relationship.
Mr. Bernardi.
We don't have
a business relationship.
So there's no compelling
business reason
for me to offer
you my protection.
But...
If we had a different kind
of relationship.
well. that might change
the way I see you.
The way I see us.
Are you trying to get the
girl that Stefano couldn't get?
You never get over
your first heartbreak.
I'm not tryin' to fix
your hurt fuckin' feelings
from way back when.
I'm tryin' to make you
some money.
Your money makin' days are over.
The last nigga who tried
to press up on me like this
is buried in the Catskills.
I prefer the Hamptons.
[Raq sighs]
Enjoy what time you got left.
'Cause it ain't much.
[dramatic music playing]
She's a real piece of ass.
And that attitude.
I get why Stefano had
such a hard on for her.
Your father loved you a lot.
He said in that letter
that you're one of
the only people I can trust.
I'm surprised by that.
I'm flattered.
but I'm surprised.
He didn't have many people
in his life that he counted one.
Me neither.
Maybe that's why he and I
got along so well.
And honestly. it seemed
like I talked at him a lot.
but. it did feel like we saw
the world in the same way.
You know who killed him?
Oh.
Jesus Christ. Laverne.
I need to know.
Take it from me.
sometimes not knowing.
is better than knowing.
Let me make that call
for myself.
What makes you think I know?
Figure he got put down
'cause of the business.
And I know you all
was workin' together.
Oh. fuck.
My father would want me to know.
I'm not so sure about that.
Did you know that your cousin
paid me an unexpected visit?
Kanan?
The fuck you want with you?
He said he was there to talk.
But I've never been part
of a productive or polite
conversation that started with
someone pointing a gun at me.
He showed up with a gat?
[ominous music playing]
♪
Hold up. Are-are you saying
Kanan put down my father?
I don't have any
firsthand knowledge.
Kanan.
That's what I heard.
But again.
I don't know if it's true.
It's true. I know it's true.
Families are complicated.
Not my family.
We simple.
We always been simple.
["One Chief Rocker"
by Vinyl Messi playing]
♪
♪ Make the people say.
ooh. aah ♪
♪ Think I won't curse ♪
♪
Put the shit on my desk.
About to do this count.
[Breeze sighs]
By the way.
my white boys been retired.
They collectin' they pensions
or insurance
or whatever the fuck you get
when you gone.
What about Bonnie and Clyde?
Nobody talkin' about
who took them out.
Shit's a fuckin' mystery.
It's a hell of a move to make.
Didn't see that shit
comin' at all.
Day seem like any other day.
Till it's not.
That how it happened
for your uncle?
You don't think
he saw that shit comin'?
I don't know what that nigga saw
or didn't see.
I ain't tryin' to think
about all that.
Just 'cause Snaps and Pops gone.
don't mean your moms
is off the hook.
Shit came from on high.
Stefano and them.
I'ma still have to
put in that work.
Do what the fuck you gotta do. nigga.
♪
Last time we sat together.
you mentioned there might be
a proffer available
to my client should she agree
to assist you
in your investigation
into various individuals
connected to organized crime.
We're curious to hear
what that might look like.
Standard "Queen for a Day"
agreement.
If Miss Thomas provides us
with information
leading to the successful
convictions
of various organized crime
targets.
we'd be willing to offer her
a plea deal and leniency
in the case against her.
I want full immunity
and witness protection.
Anything less than that. and
there ain't shit to talk about.
As Mr. Gordon here knows.
we don't get into
the specifics of the agreement
until we can evaluate
the veracity and quality
of the information.
I'm not talkin' without knowin'
what's at the other end
of the deal.
Having entered into
countless similar agreements
with individuals
like yourself before.
I can tell you
that what you're requesting
is probably within reason.
But like Special Agent Hickson
said.
we can't agree to anything
until we hear what
you have to say.
I don't want immunity and
witness protection just for me.
I want it for my son. too.
[dramatic music playing]
♪
Tough break about your father.
I'm sure it's sad for you
and your family.
I said I'd leave you alone as
long as you stayed off my radar.
But I have to ask...
I don't know who shot my father.
That's hard for me to believe.
I don't give a fuck
what you believe.
What about
Ishmael and Stephanie Henry?
I don't know who that is.
Snaps and Pop.
They got put down?
They did.
And as you know all too well.
they also were involved in
what happened to your friend.
Guess they got
what they had comin' then.
Don't do anything you're
gonna regret. Laverne.
Too late.
♪
[tense music playing]
We didn't realize
that your son was involved in
activities that might
require immunity.
I need to know we're protected.
I got enough
on Stefano Marchetti
and Pino Bernardi for you.
to burn that whole Italian shit
down to the fuckin' ground.
But you gotta make
it worth my while.
I ain't trying to have me
and my son
get cooked up
in one of Stefano's ovens.
Is that what Mr. Marchetti does?
Burns up bodies
at his smelting factories.
I said what I said.
We'll run this up the flagpole
to the A.U.S.A.
It's real easy.
You get me what I want.
I'll get you what you want.
That's all.
My gut tells me they're
going to agree to your terms.
but you're going to
have to deliver.
Their expectations
are exceedingly high.
I don't make promises
I can't keep.
But you better make sure
these Feds come correct.
'Cause once I start talkin'.
everything I ever been
and everything I ever thought
I was gonna be's gone.
♪
[gentle piano music playing]
♪ Praise the Lord ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ Lead me on ♪
-[glass clinking]
-♪ Let me... ♪
Snaps and Pop
didn't need each other.
But they wanted each other.
There's a big difference
between needin' and wantin'.
If you need someone.
that means they're givin' you
somethin'
that you can't get nowhere else.
Providing you
some sort of sustenance
that you can't do without.
But that's not love.
I don't want my woman to need me
like some medicine
she gotta take.
[laughing]
I want her to want me.
-Yeah.
-I want her to choose me.
Snaps and Pop.
they wanted each other.
And the one thing
we know about them:
They always got
what they wanted.
[crowd muttering in agreement]
To Snaps and Pop.
[all] To Snaps and Pop.
That's right.
♪
Well said Lump.
I'm not great with words.
but I make do.
[chuckling]
Yeah. well. in my experience.
it's fellas like you.
always selling themselves short.
that are playing the longest
game of all.
[chuckling]
-Touché.
-Yeah.
Hey. you were. uh.
working with a young associate
of mine for a little while.
Yeah. who's that?
Early Tyler.
Mm. Yeah.
I knew him since
before he could walk.
Yeah. Early.
Kid had a lot of promise
Tragic ending to that story.
If it makes you feel any better.
I'm pretty certain the guy
who took out Early
just got taken out himself.
It don't.
Make me feel better. that is.
I wonder if I'm the only one
who knows
how vicious you really are.
Stefano.
[tense music playing]
How underneath all that
fake inner grace.
there's a fuckin' demon who
thinks he's gonna live forever.
I don't want to live forever.
Lump.
I just wanna die last.
Take care of yourself. pal.
[dramatic music playing]
♪
[dramatic music continues]
-She's all yours. Stefano.
-Pino.
I-I missed that.
What'd you say?
Raq.
All yours.
Do what you need to do.
I got no further use for her.
Yeah. when I heard
she lost Flossie.
-I knew you'd cut bait.
-Oh.
She didn't just fuck up
everything with Flossie.
Turns out
she also passed bad drugs
to that dead judge
who was on my payroll.
And word is. this Colombian
I was working with
bought the farm because of her.
She's done to my business
what pantyhose did
to finger fuckin'.
[chuckling]
The wheels are already
in motion on her.
Oh. yeah?
That's good.
Uh.
You. uh. take care of that.
I. uh.
I like my waiter
to clear the table
as soon as I'm done eating.
Cryin' shame. though.
Pussy that good.
gonna come to a bad end.
But as the French say.
c'est la vie.
Get the fuck out of here.
huh. Pino?
She wouldn't give you
the time of fuckin' day.
You got me. my friend.
I gave it the old college try.
but somehow she was able
to resist my impish charms
and boyish good looks.
Hmm.
Look. put her out of our misery.
You have my permission.
Prego.
♪
[Kanan]
I don't believe that shit.
And even if it's true.
why the fuck are you
here tellin' me about it?
Your mother demanded
that any immunity
and witness protection deal that
we afforded her. extend to you.
Fuck outta here.
She inspired me
to do some digging on you.
I couldn't really find anything.
Just ticky-tack bullshit.
And then. all of a sudden.
your name popped up
in a pill ring investigation
out in Hempstead.
I ain't got shit to do
with Long Island.
Of course you don't.
And I'm sure you also don't have
anything to do with the murder
of the two suspects
who are cooperating with police
in that investigation.
-Glen and Shane Bellotti?
-Don't know 'em.
They were shot to death
in their backyard yesterday.
I don't fuck with white boys.
Who said they were white?
Ain't no niggas I know
called Bellotti.
Look. if my mom's
is fuckin' with y'all.
that's on her. not me.
I ain't do nothin'.
and I ain't got shit to say.
So you need to get
the fuck out my crib.
She's trying to protect you.
Kanan.
And I assume that's because
she knows something about you
that I don't know yet.
But I'm gonna find out.
and then we'll have a very
different conversation.
Your mother loves you.
That's why she's doing this.
And if you care about her.
you'll encourage her
to take this deal.
Whether you're a part
of it or not.
She's got a target on her back.
Kanan.
If she doesn't take this deal.
she'll be dead in a week.
♪
[door closes]
[Raq]
Flossie.
I know you not tryin'
to talk to me right now.
Not now or later.
No good reason
for you to help me.
but I know you got connects
to Stefano Marchetti.
and I'm wonderin'
if you can pass word
I'm tryin' to sit down with him.
You lied to me.
Your brother is dead
because of you.
You don't deserve my help
or my time.
White bitches always like Marvin
'cause he a punchline to them.
Some goofy-ass nigga
they think they can laugh at.
Then they bump up against me.
and they ain't laughin' no more.
'Cause I ain't out here
to make white bitches laugh
I'm out here to make this money.
and ain't shit funny about that.
You're not funny.
You're fucking tragic.
And I've already had
enough tragedy in my life.
Good luck.
[disheartening music playing]
♪
[hip-hop music playing
in background]
♪
-Shit heavy.
-Block workin'.
♪
[hip-hop music continues]
What you know about that shit
with my moms?
Doin' the math.
Gettin' ready
to solve the problem.
What if we didn't do that. though?
I'm just sayin'.
what if we put her out on some
go away and never come back
type shit?
Let her run.
Let her walk.
And tell her don't never step
into New York again.
♪
Thought you was okay
with what's gotta be done?
If the shit has to happen.
it has to happen.
Maybe it's another way to do it.
It ain't my call. brother.
Like I said. word came down
from that parmesan-ass nigga.
It don't feel like he gonna
be convinced otherwise.
Stefano got no love
for your moms.
Not at all.
He want her gone.
They've agreed to
everything you've asked for.
and now they want an answer.
So my son part of the deal.
Apparently.
Adrian Tanner paid Kanan a visit
and made the offer.
but it didn't go well.
Your son wasn't receptive.
In fact. he kicked agent Tanner
out of his apartment.
That's 'cause Kanan
wasn't raised to be no snitch.
How the fuck am I gonna
bring up my kid one way.
and then do the opposite
of that?
You and your son are
in very different situations.
You either a snitch or you not.
This deal is a lifeline for you.
Your only one.
Kanan right.
Fuck the Feds.
Tell the F.B.I. kiss my ass.
I ain't going out like that.
[scooter engine revving]
Yo Kanan.
Young boys wanna get down.
We got to work for 'em?
[hip-hop music playing]
What they call y'all?
-Jamie.
-Tommy.
You live in Southside?
[hip-hop music continues]
♪ I'm the best in the biz ♪
Nah.
You niggas is too young.
Come back when y'all ain't
fuckin' with Happy Meals
no more.
♪ I'm the best in the biz ♪
♪
[engine revs]
The mortician did
a really nice job.
I'll give you some time alone.
[gentle music playing]
♪
I asked you many times
whether you'd have
mixed emotions
if there was ever
an issue with your mother.
I know.
And you said you wouldn't.
That's what I said.
So what's changed?
Started to think
that maybe I don't want
this shit on my head.
I got a lot on it already.
and I don't know
that I need any more right now.
You mean Marvin.
Him and everyone else. man.
I'm not scared
of puttin' niggas down.
I'm not.
Not at all.
Almost took out my moms myself
a while back.
The shit got ill.
went another direction.
Point is. I was ready to do
that work myself back then.
Yeah. but now you. uh.
you have reservations.
Your mother insulted me. Kanan.
And while it may
not seem like it to you.
her insult has business
implications for me.
I can't afford to let
insults go unanswered.
She just partnered up
with another nigga.
The shit happens all the time.
No. no. not to me it doesn't.
Look. somethin' in me-
somethin' I didn't even know
was there no more-
is tellin' me
that I don't want this.
And maybe it's cause of
what happened to my uncle.
but maybe not.
Maybe it's just that it
don't sit right with me.
I'm just startin' to feel like
for all the shit my mom's done.
this ain't how it should go.
I give everything I got
for five more minutes
with my mother. kid.
And not a day goes by
when I-I don't feel
that hole in my heart
that she left behind
when she passed.
Now listen.
I'd consider letting her live.
but she'd have to do somethin'
for me first.
[tense music playing]
♪
[dramatic music playing]
-[engine accelerates]
-[tires squeal]
♪
[indistinct conversations]
[siren wailing in distance]
♪
Don't trust me enough
to meet at the crib.
Hell. no.
I need witnesses.
Can't blame you for that.
I'm sorry about Uncle Marvin.
For what you did.
or him bein' gone?
Both.
Heard you told them Feds you
don't want no part of that deal.
That ain't me.
Me neither.
Got shook for a minute
and lost my head.
but then I remembered who I am.
I'ma fall for this flag
before I fuck with these feds.
Anyone who want it
can come get it.
And that includes you too.
I don't want that. though.
That's why I reached out.
I spoke to Stefano.
He said he'd let you go.
But you gotta do something
for him.
[Raq]
What the fuck he want me to do?
[Kanan]
I don't know.
But whatever it is.
it's gotta be better
-than you bein'...
-Dead.
Stefano want me dead.
[Raq scoffs]
Shit.
Up until right now.
I thought you did. too.
Remember when I used
to put you to bed at night
with that warm milk?
How you'd say you
never wanted me to die.
How you always wanted
me to be there for you.
Psh.
Now look at this shit.
Still don't want you to die.
That's the nicest shit
you said to me in years.
Talk to Stefano.
Hear him out.
I blame myself
for what's happened. Kanan.
For what you did.
For what I did.
For what I didn't do.
And that don't mean
I forgive you for everything.
I don't.
I can't.
You took my brothers from me.
♪
But also know that shit
don't happen without me.
Because I raised you.
I made you.
You're mine.
All mine.
The good and the bad.
And I put you in this shit.
so it's all on me.
It's always gonna be on me.
And I know it
don't feel like it for you-
And I get why it don't-
But I loved you
in a way that I could.
Didn't always come out right.
And it wasn't always enough.
But it's what I could give you.
and how I could give it.
You care about me
like you sayin' you do.
you wanna talk to Stefano.
You love me. Kanan?
You-you my mother.
That don't mean nothin'.
No matter how fucked up
you been.
some part of me still keep
believin' you gonna be better.
You gonna be who I want.
Who I need.
I've been waitin' for you
to be that to me.
but you keep lettin' me down.
It's fucked up when the person
that tried to take your pride
is the same one you
want to make proud.
See. you don't never stop
wantin' your mother
to care about you.
even when they ain't done
shit to show that they can.
But it's too late for all that.
Look what I done.
Look what you done.
We can't fix
all that wrong shit.
But maybe we could do
this one thing right.
Ain't gotta end
like this for you.
[gentle music playing]
I'm sorry.
♪
Talk to Stefano.
Ah. I felt more comfortable.
when Snaps and Pop were around.
Felt like there was
an adult in the room.
I'm hesitant to turn over
the whole business to you
and the rest of them
fucking teenyboppers over there.
You ain't gonna have no
problems with me or my people.
We a well oiled machine
in Southside.
Well just make sure your
well oiled machine
ain't a goddamn wood chipper
grinding on my fucking balls.
Now look who's here.
[chuckles]
Ah!
Hey. give us a minute.
But. uh. don't venture too far.
How are you. ma'am?
-Fuck you. nigga.
-[Stefano chuckles]
A kind word for
everyone from you. huh?
Come on sit. sit.
[organ music playing]
[organ music continues]
You do this for me.
and then you go.
within twenty four hours.
You stay a minute longer.
and the deal is off
and you're as good as dead.
Why would I do this work for you
if I can't ever go back
to my life here in New York?
Because if you don't do it.
you won't even make it back
to your car tonight.
[tense music playing]
Do this for me.
and then you leave
New York the next day
and you don't ever come back.
Don't matter to me where you go.
just as long
as it's far from here.
[tense music continues]
Don't seem like I got much
of a choice.
Well. look at it this way.
if you were ugly.
you already be dead.
♪
[gentle knocking]
Juke! It's me!
[knocking continues]
[exhales loudly]
♪
[melancholy music playing]
What's the word?
Counts good.
Drove by 150.
Them niggas is runnin' through
they work fast.
Just sent over to re-up.
Heard your moms might
get this pass after all.
Respect. nigga.
you lookin' out for the fam.
I get it.
I'd do the same for mines.
And make sure the tails
are off the shrimp.
[knocking at door]
I'm paying you $10 a piece.
and you want me to do
all the fuckin' work.
[indistinct voices on TV]
[TV] He got an offer
from Florida State...
[sighing]
[TV] Florida. well... they got
mosquitoes down there.
[sighing]
Well looks like I'm
gonna get the girl after all.
I guess so.
[TV]
What are you talking about?
Coach. she's my fiancée.
[indistinct voices on TV]
I was surprised
to hear from you.
But. I guess I'm hard to resist.
Not like you think.
Fuckin' Stefano.
[gunshot]
[dramatic music playing]
♪
Juke.
[tense music playing]
What's going on?
I'm sorry Aunt Raq.
For what?
I don't understand.
And if I tried to make you
understand. you still wouldn't.
But it's somethin' I gotta do.
[Raq scoffs]
[tense music playing]
This about Marvin?
That wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
I know.
Talk to me. juke.
Why you doin' this?
Kanan.
What Kanan gotta do with me?
-[gunshot]
-[glass shatters]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music playing]
Bullshit.
You gonna know
it's real soon enough.
Why wouldn't you
just come after me?
That was the plan.
And then I saw
you and her together.
and I realized droppin' you
wasn't gonna hurt enough.
You wouldn't feel the pain
for as long
as I want you to feel it.
I want you to have nothin'
nigga.
Just like me.
I want you to go through
your life alone.
with nobody to give a fuck
whether you live or die.
You gonna be alive.
But everyone around
you who cared...
Gone.
And that shit way worse
than bein' dead.
You just as alone as me Juke.
World just as cold for you.
Knowin' I did this to you.
gon' keep me warm
for a long while.
And that's enough for me.
I could just kill you myself.
Have at it. nigga.
I don't give a fuck.
[dramatic music playing]
She never loved you anyway.
Right at the end.
she begged me to do you
instead of her.
[dramatic music playing]
♪
[older Kanan] All this shit
don't explain everything.
'cause nothin' explains
everything.
You niggas want to know
why this shit happen
and why this shit didn't.
This was never gon' be all that.
couldn't be.
'Cause my story didn't end here.
Shit. in a lot of ways this was
just the beginning of me.
What I turned into.
who I ended up bein'.
See. this isn't just my story.
this is our story.
And now it's your story.
But like I said all along.
more than anything.
this is a Southside
Jamaica Queens story.
[Ghetto Qu'ran (Forgive Me)
[by 50 Cent playing]
♪ Uh-huh. uh-huh. uh-huh.
Southside ♪
♪ What y'all niggas
know about the dirty South? ♪
♪ One time ♪
♪ Lord forgive me.
for I've sinned ♪
♪ Over and over again
just to stay on top ♪
♪ I recall memories
filled with sin ♪
♪ Over and over again. and again
(And again and again) ♪
♪ Yo. when you hear talk
of the Southside ♪
♪ You hear talk of the Team ♪
♪ See niggas feared Prince
and respected 'Preme ♪
♪ For all you slow
motherfuckers ♪
♪ I'ma break it down iller ♪
♪ See Preme was the businessman
and Prince was the killer ♪
♪ Remember. he used to push
the bulletproof BM. uh-huh ♪
♪ His hair'll get you seasick.
I sat back and peeped shit ♪
♪ They rolled with E-Z Wider
then. they ain't get blunted ♪
♪ Had the whole projects
working for 50 on 500 ♪
♪ As a youth.
all I ever did was sell crack ♪
♪ I used to idolize Cat ♪
♪ Hurt me to my heart to hear
that nigga snitched on Pap ♪
♪ How he go out like that? ♪
♪ Rumors in the hood was
just was snitching ♪
♪ I ain't believe that ♪
[TV]
Michael. show him the bedroom.
Okay. come on Eddie.
Florida. ain't no way in the
world that boy gonna stay-
-[baby crying]
-He is going.
-Shh. shh. shh.
-[baby crying]
What he cryin' about?
He just got here.
Maybe 'cause he know
you about to be his uncle.
I'ma kick your ass. Lou-Lou
He's beautiful Raq.
looks just like you.
-You think?
-I do.
[sucks teeth]
Kanan's okay.
He gonna need to toughen
the fuck up. though.
Ain't nobody got time
for all this cryin'.
He a baby. Marvin.
He my nephew.
When me and him out on the
avenue.
I need to know he
can go toe to toe.
[Kanan crying]
Yo. Lou-Lou. let's go get this
grub. I'm starvin'.
Always starving.
That's cause I'm busy carryin'
this whole fuckin' family
on my back.
[Marvin makes racing sound]
[Kanan fussing]
We'll see you in a little bit.
Kanan.
You cry all you want.
'Cause I'm here.
And I'm always gonna be here.
I ain't never gonna let
nothin' bad ever happen to you.
Not while I got you.
Remember. it's you and me Kanan.
Always.
[Little Child Runnin' Wild
by Curtis Mayfield playing]
♪ Little child ♪
♪ Runnin' wild ♪
♪ Watch a while ♪
♪ You see he never smiles ♪
♪ Broken home ♪
♪ Father gone ♪
♪ Mama tired ♪
♪ So he's all alone ♪